wolfcrow.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

At wolfcrow we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. This Website Privacy Policy has been provided by the legal resource www.diylegals.co.uk and reviewed and approved by their solicitors.

This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit or make a purchase from wolfcrow.com (the “Site”).

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. So please do review this Policy regularly.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

**Information We Collect**

In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
  * Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase.
  * Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.
  * When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, Paypal or Stripe or other payment gateway information), email address, and phone number.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer fin order to assist us in improving our website.

We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

We use Google Analytics remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. This allows us to provide targeted advertising in the future. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the [DoubleClick opt-out page](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en#display_optout) or the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).”

**Use of Your Information**

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  * To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
  * To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receive such information.
  * To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.
  * We use the information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).
  * To provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
  * To optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.

Where your consent has been provided in advance we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you. Where such consent has been provided it can be withdrawn by you at any time.

**Storing Your Personal Data**

In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We do our upmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is treated stored securely.

Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, Sending such information is entirely at your own risk.

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada, India and the United States.

**Data Retention**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**Minors**

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

**Disclosing Your Information**

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  * In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
  * Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
  * To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.
  * We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.
  * We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**Behavioral Advertising**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

  * FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
  * GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
  * BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
  * Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/
  * We also use dedicated CRM software and if you would like to be removed from all future communications, or you would like to see or change any information about you, please send us a an email on the email address below.

**Third Party Links**

On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.

**Access to Information**

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a fee of $10 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information.

**Contacting Us**

Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy at info@wolfcrow.com.
